Guide to the Arthur H. Dean papers, 1937-1980
Dean, Arthur H. papers, 1937-1980
- Series V. Subject Files
  - Sullivan and Cromwell
    - Sullivan and Cromwell: Bound briefs and case material (Box 149-150)
    - Sullivan and Cromwell: Petroleum (anti-trust); O'Mahoney Reports (anti-trust) (Box 151)
    - Sullivan and Cromwell: Anti-trust (Box 152)
    - Corporate Re-Organization (Box 153)
    - Kennecott vs. Federal Trade Commission (Box 154)
  - Teagle Foundation
    - Teagle Foundation, Inc: 1963 - 1980 (Box 133)
  - National Citizens Committee for Community Relations (Civil Rights)
    - Civil Rights: National Citizens Committee for Community Relations (Dean was Chairman) 1964 - 67 (Box 134)
    - Civil Rights: 1964 - 67 (Box 135)
  - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities
    - Committee For Corporate Support of American Universities: (formerly, Informal Advisory Committee on Corporate Aid to Higher Education, a program for Harvard College) 1957 - 68 (Box 136)
    - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities: 1969 - 74 (Box 137)
    - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities: Committee Brochures, 1959 - 71; Minutes of Meetings, 1966 - 72 (Box 138)
  - Twentieth-Century Fund
    - 20th Century Fund: Arthur Dean, Chairman of Committee on Economic Needs of Older People (Box 142)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children: (later, Foundation for Child Development) 1948 - 1975 (Box 143)
  - Corporate Directorships
    - Corporate Directorships: Dean's Directorships listed A - Z (Box 145)
  - Treaty Powers, Amendment of
    - Treaty Powers, Amendment of (Box 147)
  - Conference on Indian - American Relations
    - Conference on Indian - American Relations (Box 148)
  - Other Subject Files
    - Subject Files: Allen W. Dulles, 1953 - 69; American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1963 - 65; American College of Trial Lawyers, 1955 - 64; Dinner Party Group, 1955 - 60; Hampton Institute, Centennial Fund, 1964 - 69; International Academy of Astronautics, 1961 - 69; John Foster Dulles, 1952 - 73 (and estate of Dulles); Prince Bernhard, 1976; Ralph Bunche Memorial Committee, 1972 - 74; Waddill Catchings, 1953 - 60 (Box 131)
    - Business Income Study Group: Dean speeches; Study Group Report; Correspondence 1948 - 52 (Box 132)
    - Subject Files: Advisory Committee of Federal Government and Higher Education, 1960 - 61; American Council of Learned Societies, 1963 - 67; Communism in Education Committee, 1953; Educational Television and Radio Center, 1953 - 56; Foreign Policy Association, 1948 - 67; International House, 1956 - 65; International Law Fund, 1960 - 61; Lafayette Fellowship Foundation, 1955 - 62; National Fund for Medical Education, 1957 - 59; Twentieth Century Fund, 1950 - 1956 (Box 139)
    - Subject Files: International Chamber of Commerce, Inc., 1963 - 74; Pilgrims of the United States, 1956 - 77; Navy League of the United States, 1964; St. John of Jerusalem, American Society of the Most Venerable Order of the Hospital of, 1960 - 69; Voluntary Credit Restraint Committee, 1951 - 52 (Box 144)
    - Subject Files: American Metals; Barkley Bill; Changing Non-redeemable Preferred Stock into Redeemable Stock; Securities Exchange Committee; Shields Plan, (rights offerings) (Box 146)
  - Additional Material
    - Additional Material (Box 155)